A hilarious look at the universe's most fervent fans.
Trekkies is a documentary film directed by Roger Nygard.
Denise Crosby takes a first look at the huge fans of "Star Trek" from around
America and how the series has affected and shaped their lives.
Self, played by Denise Crosby.
Self, played by Barbara Adams.
Self, played by Majel Barrett.
Self, played by James Doohan.
Self, played by DeForest Kelley.
Self, played by Leonard Nimoy.
Trekkies is a 1997 documentary film directed by Roger Nygard about
the devoted fans of Gene Roddenberry's Star Trek.
It is the first film released by Paramount Vantage, then known as Paramount Classics, and is presented by Denise Crosby, best
known for her portrayal of Security Chief Tasha Yar on the first season of Star Trek: The Next Generation.
The film explores themes of pop culture, fan culture,
space opera, fan convention, fandom.